(Leonard:)Easy-peasy, ooh, so breezy.
(Stuart:)Hey, what's up?
(Raj:)I'm here to put
the crib together.
(Stuart:)Ooh, sorry, I already did it.
Oh, I don't know if you realize
this, but I bought that crib.
(Stuart:)Oh, yeah, I read about that
on WhoGivesACrap.com
(Raj:)Why are you being like this?
(Stuart:)Because I love
Howard and Bernadette
(Stuart:)and if I want to keep mooching
off them, I need to be helpful.
(Raj:)Hey, this pregnancy had
(Raj:)an emotionally-needy third wheel
(Raj:)way before you came along.
(Stuart:)Why can't there be four wheels?
(Raj:)Is this what you do
when I'm not here,
(Raj:)make really good points?
Look-Look, just come in and
help me build a baby swing.